<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yinka Adesesan</title>
    <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yinka Adesesan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:38:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigr8: Improving the journey of Migrant workers to Canada using design thinking</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/immigr8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:38:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/immigr8/</guid>
      <description>Summary In our globalized world there is increased economic migration to high income countries like Canada. Economic migrants face the problem of finding relevant information without wasting precious time. The concept of a crowdsourced AI platform was proposed as a solution - by providing personalized information based on the user’s unique profile. A multi-sided business model was designed with big picture numbers showing profitability in 3 years.
Challenge To explore and identity opportunities for innovation along the Migrant worker&amp;rsquo;s immigration journey, to ideate and evaluate solutions and to create a strategy for the implementation of the tested strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupra Vision: A vision of sports driving</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/cupra-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:35:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/cupra-vision/</guid>
      <description>Summary CUPRA is an offshoot of the spanish automobile manufacturer. As a relatively new automobile brand, a major objective is to find ways to stand out in the market by finding a niche for themselves. Targeting sport driving aficionados means creating experiences that they are able to connect with. In this project, we created a concept of sports driving using digital and connectivity technology called Cupra Vision.
Challenge What does the vision of an individualised CUPRA sports driving experience look like?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkable: Designing a walking experience to discover neighbourhoods in Barcelona</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/walkable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 17:42:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/walkable/</guid>
      <description>Summary CUPRA is an offshoot of the spanish automobile manufacturer. As a relatively new automobile brand, a major objective is to find ways to stand out in the market by finding a niche for themselves. Targeting sport driving aficionados means creating experiences that they are able to connect with. In this project, we created a concept of sports driving using digital and connectivity technology called Cupra Vision.
Challenge What does the vision of an individualised CUPRA sports driving experience look like?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>