<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yinka Adesesan</title>
    <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yinka Adesesan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:56:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yinka.adesesan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Plan to Be Productive This Year (2021)</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/how-i-plan-to-be-productive-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:56:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/how-i-plan-to-be-productive-this-year/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a pretty productive year for me despite all the drama that it came with. I read a ton of books, built a personal brand and website for myself, pivoted my business and ran a logo design challenge while working on various projects for clients. One of the gamechangers that helped me level up my productivity game was bullet journaling. It provided the structure I needed in the form of an easy to use methodology for keeping track of my life that I found super helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading in 2020</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/reading-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/reading-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a trash year in a lot of respects but it was a great year for reading for me. In 2018 and 2019 I read 14 and 19 books respectively but in 2020, I managed to increase that number and read almost twice as many books as I did the previous year, ending the year having read 33 books in total. One of my main goals going into 2020 was to increase the amount of reading I got done and in a year where there weren&amp;rsquo;t as many wins as I hoped, I&amp;rsquo;m choosing to count this as a major win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Books of 2019</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/my-books-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:47:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/my-books-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>Reading has always been a big part of my life and 2019 was a big year in terms of reading for me. I was able to increase the number of book I read from 14 books in 2018 to 19 in 2019 (that&amp;rsquo;s a 35% increase). And I read really interesting books as well - both fiction and non-fiction. Below is the list of books that I read in the year 2019 organized into fiction and non-fiction which some highlights on the books that really stood out to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigr8: Improving the journey of Migrant workers</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/immigr8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:38:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/immigr8/</guid>
      <description>Summary In our globalized world there is increased economic migration to high income countries like Canada. Economic migrants face the problem of finding relevant information without wasting precious time. The concept of a crowdsourced AI platform was proposed as a solution - by providing personalized information based on the user’s unique profile. A multi-sided business model was designed with big picture numbers showing profitability in 3 years.
Challenge To explore and identity opportunities for innovation along the Migrant worker&amp;rsquo;s immigration journey, to ideate and evaluate solutions and to create a strategy for the implementation of the tested strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupra Vision: A vision of sports driving</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/cupra-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:35:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/cupra-vision/</guid>
      <description>Summary CUPRA is an offshoot of the spanish automobile manufacturer SEAT. As a relatively new automobile brand, a major objective is to find ways to stand out in the market by finding a niche for themselves. Targeting sport driving aficionados means creating experiences that they are able to connect with. In this project, we created a concept of sports driving using digital and connectivity technology called Cupra Vision.
Challenge What does the vision of an individualised CUPRA sports driving experience look like?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkable: Designing a walking experience</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/walkable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 17:42:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/projects/walkable/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Design a way to turn a passive commute into an active interaction? How do we provide the walking commuter with opportunities for exploration and adventure?
My Role Researcher / Ideation / Interaction Design
Research and Insights The team I was working with carried out in-depth interviews with walking commuters in the Gracia area of Barcelona. The following are some insights that we uncovered.
 Commuters rarely change their route to work or school for years Only 1 in 5 people have consciously explored their neighbourhoods A walking commuter’s mood changes depending on whether she is going to or coming back from work  Solution We generated some ideas but finally landed on the concept for an app that shows the user events, discounts, new spots, photospots and street art in their neighbourhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Yinka Adesesan</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 19:58:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Yinka Adesesan and I am Business designer. I help organisations understand contexts in order to create products, services and ventures with clarity. I have just concluded a Masters Diploma in Design Management from Instituto Europeo di Design Barcelona (where I focused on Business Design and Design Strategy).
Prior, I&amp;rsquo;ve had a meandering career that has spanned quite a number of domains. From Electrical Engineering (what I was trained in) and technology education, to founding and running a graphic and web development agency called Creovativ for 5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>