<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Yinka Adesesan</title>
    <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Yinka Adesesan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:56:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Plan to Be Productive This Year (2021)</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/how-i-plan-to-be-productive-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:56:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/how-i-plan-to-be-productive-this-year/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a pretty productive year for me despite all the drama that it came with. I read a ton of books, built a personal brand and website for myself, pivoted my business and ran a logo design challenge while working on various projects for clients. One of the gamechangers that helped me level up my productivity game was bullet journaling. It provided the structure I needed in the form of an easy to use methodology for keeping track of my life that I found super helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading in 2020</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/reading-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/reading-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a trash year in a lot of respects but it was a great year for reading for me. In 2018 and 2019 I read 14 and 19 books respectively but in 2020, I managed to increase that number and read almost twice as many books as I did the previous year, ending the year having read 33 books in total. One of my main goals going into 2020 was to increase the amount of reading I got done and in a year where there weren&amp;rsquo;t as many wins as I hoped, I&amp;rsquo;m choosing to count this as a major win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Books of 2019</title>
      <link>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/my-books-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:47:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yinka.adesesan.com/articles/my-books-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>Reading has always been a big part of my life and 2019 was a big year in terms of reading for me. I was able to increase the number of book I read from 14 books in 2018 to 19 in 2019 (that&amp;rsquo;s a 35% increase). And I read really interesting books as well - both fiction and non-fiction. Below is the list of books that I read in the year 2019 organized into fiction and non-fiction which some highlights on the books that really stood out to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>